ivideon.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy Policy | Ivideon

_Last updated: June 9, 2016_

MOBILE VIDEO SOLUTIONS INC (IVIDEON) is pleased to provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information we receive from you and other users of the IVIDEON service, through our software, mobile applications and our website located at [http://www.ivideon.com](http://www.ivideon.com/) (the Website). Such service, the software, mobile applications and the Website are collectively referred to in this Privacy Policy as the Service. This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us through the Service. By using the Service, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. IVIDEON reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and we will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Website at <http://www.ivideon.com/privacy>. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. Your continued use of the Service will be subject to the then-current privacy policy.

## Information We Collect

The data that we regularly collect about visitors to the Website (e.g., IP address, browser type, pages accessed, duration of visit, etc.) does not necessarily enable us to personally identify you, and that is not our intention.

We do collect personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, email address, credit card and/or bank account information, business name and address or other information that allows us to identify you or that could reasonably be used to infer your identity, when you voluntarily provide it by registering with us or using the Service. For analytical and marketing purposes, and to prevent fraud, we also collect data related to your account, such as your IP-address and ISP name, referral links, client software configuration, and payments history with third party services. Once you become a user, you may provide additional information, such as your location, to allow us to provide location-based feature. Providing additional information is optional.

To facilitate your use of the Service, IVIDEON may automatically collect certain types of information listed above when you access or use the Service. In order to collect this data, IVIDEON may utilize automated tools and files such as cookies. These automated tools and files may reside on our servers or on your computer or device. If you restrict our ability to use automated tools and files, your ability to access and use all or part of the Service may be limited or disabled completely.

## Use of Information

IVIDEON uses your personally identifiable information primarily for the following purposes: (i) to provide, test and improve our Service, features and content, (ii) to administer the Service, including to verify your authority to access the Service, (iii) to provide customer support for the Service, (iv) to fulfill requests you may make, (v) to personalize your experience, (vi) to provide or offer software updates and product announcements, and (vii) to provide you with further information from us related to the services that we believe you may find useful or interesting.

You may opt-out of receiving some or all non-Service related communications by updating your profile on the Service. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive any such communications, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications sent to you, or update your profile information.

We use information we obtain by technical means (such as the automatic recording performed by our servers or through the use of cookies) for the above purposes and in order to monitor and analyze use of the Service, for the Service’s technical administration, to increase the Service’s functionality and user-friendliness, to better tailor it to your needs, to generate and derive useful data and information concerning the interests, characteristics and website use behavior of our users, and to verify that users of the Service meet the criteria required to process their requests.

## Controlling Your Personal Information

IVIDEON may make available to users chat rooms, forums, message boards, and other interactive features. You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g. user name, e-mail address) via forums, postings, profiles or other areas of the Website, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected, correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from other posters or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of IVIDEON. Please do not post any personal information on the Website or in other areas that you expect to keep private.

## Disclosure

IVIDEON does not share your personal information with third parties or the public except as set forth herein.

Third Parties. We may share your personal information with our third-party service providers, such as data storage providers, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, and payment processing, which supplement and improve the Service. These service providers may have access to personal information as needed to perform their functions and we will use commercially reasonable efforts to prevent such third parties from disclosing your personal information, except for the purpose of providing the services in question. We do not sell your personal information to third parties for their own marketing purposes.

Research. We may use and disclose to third parties information we collect in aggregated, non-personally identifiable form for research and informational purposes and to help us make sales, marketing and business decisions.

Mergers & Acquisitions. IVIDEON may disclose your personally identifiable information, as necessary, in connection with a transfer or sale to another entity of all or substantially all of IVIDEON stock or assets in IVIDEON line of business to which this Privacy Policy relates or upon any bankruptcy or other corporate reorganization. We will continue to ensure the confidentiality of any personal information and give affected users notice before personal information is transferred or becomes subject to any new privacy policy of an acquirer of our business.

Special Circumstances. In addition, IVIDEON may disclose your personally identifiable information (a) when requested to do so by law enforcement agencies; (b) when obliged to do so under applicable law; (c) to protect the property rights of IVIDEON or a third party; (d) to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity that IVIDEON may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable, or (e) when given permission to do so by you.

## Links

For your convenience, we may provide links to certain third party websites or referrals to certain third parties’ products or services. If you choose to visit a third party’s website or use its products or services, please be aware that the third party’s privacy policy, and not the IVIDEON privacy policy, will govern your activities and any information you disclose while interacting with the third party.

## Storage and Security

IVIDEON maintains data centers around the world to serve its international community of users. Our data centers located in the United States serve users from the United States, Canada, Japan, and South America. Data from users in Europe, the UK, and the Middle East is stored in our data centers in Germany, the Netherlands and the UK. Southeast Asia, Australia and Oceania are served by our data centers in Singapore. Finally, users from the CIS countries have their data stored in data centers located in the Russian Federation, Ukraine and Kazakhstan.

We have put in place reasonable physical and technical measures to safeguard the information we collect in connection with the Services. However, please note that although we take reasonable steps to protect your information, no website, Internet transmission, computer system or wireless connection is completely secure.

## Collection of Information from Children

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information relating to children. In the event that we learn that we have collected personally identifiable information from anyone under 13 years of age without prior parental consent, we will take steps to promptly delete such information. By providing your personal information to IVIDEON, through the Service, you represent that you are 13 years of age or older.

## International Visitors and Users

The Website is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting from the other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal data to the United States which does not have the same data protection laws as other regions and by providing your personal data you consent to:

(1) The use of your personal data for the purposes identified above in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and

(2) The transfer of your personal data to the United States as indicated above.

## No Error-Free Performance

IVIDEON does not guarantee error-free performance under this Privacy Policy. We may not always catch an unintended privacy issue, despite our reasonable efforts to do so. Accordingly, we welcome your feedback regarding any privacy concerns that you may have, including how we can improve this Privacy Policy. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with this Privacy Policy and will take prompt corrective action when we learn of any failure to comply with it.

## Legal Notices

This Privacy Policy is subject to the terms in our Terms of Use, available for review at <http://www.ivideon.com/terms-of-service>, including terms regarding limitations on damages, disclaimers of warranties, and resolution of disputes. Our Terms of Use take precedence over any conflicting provision in this Privacy Policy.

## Questions

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us at [support@ivideon.com](mailto:support@ivideon.com).

The most recent copy of the Privacy Policy can be found here: <http://www.ivideon.com/privacy>.
